Spring was here at last.
Hey, you broke it!
I did?
Tired out already?
Me? Not even close!
Keep at it!
Everyone sure is going at it.
One, two! One, two! One, two!
You disgrace the Demonic Kingdom
with your feebleness!
Give me ten more laps!
What?!
They're sure hard at work.
Discipline fosters nobility, after all.
Why is everyone out exercising?
For the martial arts competition, of course.
Even the girls from the town office
are taking part?
Village Clerks
They don't seem like fighters to me.
Holding power in the Demonic Kingdom
requires martial prowess.
It does?
Hey! No slacking!
I've been found.
Excuse me, then.
It's time to fight!
You got me...
Hey!
You gotta do it right!
Hrngh!
Everyone seems excited
about the competition.
Seven hundred and one!
Seven hundred and two!
I'm headed home to train.
What for?
I haven't used my full strength
since coming here,
so I need some practice.
That was you out of practice?
Far from my best.
If she used her full strength...
Blaargh!
Actually!
We need a referee for the event,
and I don't know a thing
about martial arts.
But that sounds boring-
The referee needs to be strong.
Someone who can show everyone
what true strength is!
I guess you have a point.
Mayor!
I'm headed home to train.
Roooar!
Baaah!
I need two referees!
Two experts!
Only two truly skilled fighters
can be referees!
Good point!
Makes sense.
Great! Counting on you!
But I still want to fight.
Yeah, huh?
We settled on having them as referees
with their own mock battle.
Why the creepy laugh?
I'll finally be able to punch you again, Tia.
Oh, Lulucy, has your fist ever
reached me even once before?
Hasn't it?
Now that I think about it,
they did say they were rivals.
You just ate one.
Now that I think about it,
they did say they were rivals.
Did I?
There, there.
Things sure are getting violent, huh?
You're not joining in?
I'll act as healer for
anyone who gets injured.
I thought you'd want to blow things up.
Witness the greatest explosion ever!
Explosives aren't meant for people.
On that we agree...
We should make an arena where all our
residents and guests can watch and enjoy.
Stage
We'll have a stage and stadium seating.
Seats
Let's make space for shops
and restaurants too.
Stall Space
They'll be able to watch and eat?
How fancy.
We'll have to think up some
good festival food.
Refreshing.
Before long, the day was here.
Look!
Wow!
Thank you for inviting us here this day.
Demon Lord's Daughter
Yuri
Yeah, been a while.
This is my father.
The name is Galgardo.
Titular Demon Lord of the
Demonic Kingdom of Galgardo.
The Demon Lord?
What should I do?
I don't know their customs...
Father, we need no excessive formalities.
Right, yes.
I am Yuri's dad. Nice to meet you.
Thank you for joining us.
I hope my daughters
aren't causing you trouble.
No, of course not.
He's soft-spoken,
but he's important back in his kingdom
and must be pretty strong.
Excuse me.
You must be the mayor.
I am. And you are...?
This here's my father.
And my grandfather!
Which means...
You're the Emperor Dragon?
Emperor Dragon
Nothing more than an honorary title.
You can call me Doze.
Sir Doze, then.
Is that truly the legendary dragon who...?
Simply Doze.
Yes. Now say no more.
And with you?
Oh, this? He's the Demon Lord.
Wait, really?
Yup. Yuri's father.
So you lead the Demonic Kingdom?
Indeed.
That I do.
Thank you all for gathering with us.
We will now begin the Great Tree Village's
first martial arts competition.
This should be good.
I-Indeed.
Everyone sure is excited.
This is the largest event
we've ever held, after all.
You know, this was supposed to be
seating for our guests.
This is better. Just sit with confidence.
Well, uhhh, try not to get hurt
out there, everyone.
The crowd went wild.
I'm getting nervous. Let's do our best!
And we started with our first half
where anyone could join.
The rules were simple.
They'd draw lots for one-on-one battles.
Open Tournament Rules
To win, you had to either
knock your opponent out of the ring,
or we'd decide based on their headbands.
They were infused with protective magic
and would unravel whenever
a decisive blow was landed.
The first round pit the clerk Rosalind
against the beastwoman Mamu.
Ready?
Set...
Fight!
Wow, a real fight, right from the start.
I feel bad for thinking they'd just be
swinging sticks around.
Expectations
The winner is Rosalind!
I'd like to see the healer...
Ooo, you've taken some serious damage.
Healing...
Oh my gosh, I'm really sorry!
I'll be fine.
Paging all combatants!
I can handle broken limbs,
but reattaching things is harder work.
so please refrain from tearing anything off!
What a terrifying announcement.
Round Two
Hmph. Was that all?
Hup!
Donovan wins!
I didn't stand a chance.
Give it thirty more years and you'll be great.
That's hardly enough to stop an elder dwarf.
They walked through the
monster-infested woods to get here.
True.
More of them have shown up since, too.
I heard you have alcohol here.
Sure took your time.
Prepare to face Gruwald Raby Coll!
No! Stay away!
That's it!
Roaju wins!
I ran too far?!
Hiyah!
The winner.
Accomplishment.
There were some more peaceful battles.
The final battle of the open tournament
was between Flow and Sena.
Flow was using a sword and magic.
But Sena was... bare handed?
Flow! You look so cool!
Make us proud!
I'm your biggest fan!
Ready?
Fight!
Powers of the wind!
Get her!
You can do it!
Whoa!
Wow.
They're much more aggressive than usual.
Since when was Sena a grappler?
F-L-O-W! You're amazing!
There! Finish her!
Hup!
She grabbed her back?!
Uh-oh...
Aaah!
Uhhh...
They both fell together, so...
that's a tie!
What an excellent fight.
That concludes the open tournament.
Congratulations.
Your battles were more impressive
than I imagined.
The winners were given honorary medals.
Please give another round of applause
for our brave combatants.
That was awesome!
Flow...
You were so cool!
Yes?
You almost won!
Ahhh...
But that was only the first half.
I wonder what the warrior
tournament will be like.
Hang on, I don't see
the mayor's name on the list.
Shh, I'm sure it's supposed to be a secret.
Forgive me, I almost spoiled the surprise.
I'm not some secret
unlockable character, okay?
We will now begin the warrior tournament!
Things were simpler in this half.
Winners would emerge when one party
was knocked out or gave up.
There were no restrictions on weapons.
Only those capable of fighting
under these rules were allowed in.
They'd fight according to a tournament
bracket with the first battle between
Warrior Tournament Round 1
Inferno Wolf
Uno
Uno the inferno wolf
Lamia
Junea
and Junea the lamia.
I can do this.
It's one-on-one this time...
She seems pained.
The wolves did nearly exterminate
her people, after all.
Oh yeah, that was my fault.
Let the battle begin!
Wow!
She's making full use of her form.
This is what I had long trained for.
Do you concede?
Well?
I concede!
Never knew they could do that.
Stories of a single inferno wolf
destroying entire towns might be true.
Uno wins!
The next round pitted Daga the lizardman
against one of Zabuton's offspring, Makura.
Flashback
You want to join?
Okay, but we can't just call you
"Zabuton's offspring" then.
You need a name...
You're rounder, so maybe "Makura,"
which means pillow?
Oh, I take it you like it.
New Name: Makura
Hup!
Hiyah!
It just keeps running.
Daga has the upper hand.
Are you sure?
There's nowhere left to run...
I am defeated.
The winner is Makura!
I stood no chance...
Should it be that strong?
Good luck!
Go get 'em!
Next, round three!
Ya the mountain elf versus
our guest from Howling Village, Garf!
Ready...
Fight!
Brace yourself.
This looks easy for Garf.
He seems pretty composed.
He's the greatest warrior
in Howling Village!
Must be hard to face him
with a weapon like that.
It puts her at a disadvantage.
Which leaves her only one option.
A single strike charged with magic!
Hiyaaah!
Oop!
Whew, that was close.
Aww, I didn't hit him at the right angle!
Ya gave up, making Garf
the winner of round three.
Go get 'em!
Next was round four.
Next...
Representing the high elves is Lea.
Her opponent, the angel Granmaria!
The rules will be altered this round.
Falling from the stage
will no longer end the match.
That wouldn't be fair when one can fly.
You're not using your usual weapon?
No...
I would be unable to hold back
if I used my spear.
I'm quite fine facing your full force.
Ready?
Fight!
You do well hiding yourself. However...
from up above, all is clear...
Hiyah!
Well? Care to concede?
Never!
You may have thought pinning someone
small like me would earn you the win.
But your entire weight is not
half that of my spear!
Now you're just being rash!
Fine then!
Which of us is rash now?
All I need to do is stand and I win.
But I can't...
Is that a tie?
That was an epic battle.
But the truly epic battles had not yet begun.
Warrior Tournament Round 5
Tia
Kudel
Don't hold back now.
Yes, of course not...
Begin...
Tia wins!
Oww! No one can beat that!
Warrior Tournament Round 6
Corone
Lu Lulucy
Come on then.
I'm done for...
Begin...
The winner is Lu!
I thought I was done for.
Fully Healed
Ugh...
It's finally time!
I need to record my sister
in all her gallant glory!
Is it really okay for our healer
to be up here?
Why?
She'll never get hurt.
She won't?
Lu!
Shall we then?
Let's.
Ready...
Fight!
Wha?!
What is this?
I don't even understand
what's going on!
Lu! Lu! Lu!
Is everyone else following along?
Okay then...
There they are!
This spear really does
boost my physical abilities.
My eyes can now just barely keep up.
This is incredible!
There! Blow her up!
Here I go!
What?!
Just like I said.
Finally able to punch you again.
Well, let's have it then!
Oof...
Take that!
They're really going at it.
Enough!
They look like they're having fun, too.
If this were a shonen manga,
they'd become good friends after this.
You're not half bad.
If this were a shonen manga,
they'd become good friends after this.
I could say the same.
How dare you!
How dare I what?!
Maybe these punches come from
a place of friendship...
Ow! We're supposed to take turns!
Maybe these punches come from
a place of friendship...
I don't remember that rule!
Maybe these punches come from
a place of friendship...
I don't remember that rule!
Sheesh.
That's not fair!
It's just not fair!
A safe distance away
The winner is Tia.
It's just not fair!
I guess that does it.
Darling!
Tia is being mean to me!
Oof! Oww! It hurts! Oww!
You can't pull that now!
After a phenomenal battle,
Tia beat Lu.
And her opponent in
the final round was...
Huh?
I'm not cut out for this!
This takes me back.
Makura, congratulations on winning
the warrior tournament.
The prize is this crown, but...
That's where you're going to wear it?
We didn't stand a chance.
Thank you all once again.
I'll say just one thing.
Each battle was tremendous.
Go now and rest-
Hey!
What about our turn?
Boo! Boo!
Protest
We want to battle!
Oh, right.
To close us off, our referees
will hold a mock battle.
Here I go!
Bring it on!
Word is the explosion was visible
from the Demonic Kingdom.
The shops were blown away,
but at least we have our drink!
Thank goodness.
She's the one who went all out.
Like you didn't.
You could at least hold back.
Me too!
I did.
Hold back more, then.
I'm the one who gave them the go ahead.
Hakuren won the round.
You need more practice.
Waaah!
I did see Lasty land an explosive uppercut.
I wonder if her blind spot is down below?
It's been a long time
since a battle has riled me up!
Care to take me on in battle, Demon Lord?
You're too funny.
Despite it all, things went quite well.
Yup.
If you want to call this going well.
Everyone had a good time, though.
That's good enough for a festival.
We'll need to rethink the structural integrity,
but when will we host the next one?
Uhhh...
I think I'm good for a while...
Next time
Another Peaceful Day
Episode 5